Guide to the George Ellery Hale Papers HaleGE
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Correspondence and Records Relating to Organizations, 1863–1937; 2; 14 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_01)
  - National Research Council, 1903–1937; 3; National Research Council (U.S.); 3 linear feet (Carton 1, Reel 50–54, Carton 3)
    - World Cotton Conference, 1918–1919; HaleGE_02_0C_060_10; 45 pages (Box 60, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 709 to 754.
    - Division of Anthropology and Psychology, 1917–1921; HaleGE_02_0C_061_01; 77 pages (Box 61, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 755 to 832.
    - Division of Biology and Agriculture, 1919–1923; HaleGE_02_0C_061_02; 18 pages (Box 61, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 833 to 851.
    - Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology, 1921–1922; HaleGE_02_0C_061_03; 23 pages (Box 61, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 852 to 875.
    - Division of Educational Relations, 1917–1925; HaleGE_02_0C_061_04; 269 pages (Box 61, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 876 to 1145.
    - Division of Engineering, 1918–1924; HaleGE_02_0C_061_05; 96 pages (Box 61, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 20 to 116.
    - Division of Foreign Relations, 1919–1936; HaleGE_02_0C_061_06; 606 pages (Box 61, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 117 to 720.
    - Division of General Relations, undated; HaleGE_02_0C_062_01; 2 pages (Box 62, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 721 to 723.
    - Division of Geology and Geography, 1919–1925; HaleGE_02_0C_062_02; 50 pages (Box 62, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 724 to 774.
    - Division of Industrial Relations, 1919; HaleGE_02_0C_062_03; 16 pages (Box 62, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 775 to 790.
    - Division of Medical Sciences, 1920–1921; HaleGE_02_0C_062_04; 9 pages (Box 62, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 791 to 800.
    - Division of Medicine, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_062_05; 62 pages (Box 62, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 801 to 863.
    - Division of Physical Sciences, 1918–1922; HaleGE_02_0C_062_06; 55 pages (Box 62, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 864 to 919.
    - Division of Sciences and Technology, undated; HaleGE_02_0C_062_07; 8 pages (Box 62, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 920 to 928.
    - Division of Research Extension, 1919–1921; HaleGE_02_0C_062_08; 43 pages (Box 62, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 929 to 972.
    - Division of States Relations, 1919–1927; HaleGE_02_0C_062_09; 115 pages (Box 62, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 53, frames 973 to 1089.
    - Executive Board (Interim Committee), 1921–1937; HaleGE_02_0C_062_10; 273 pages (Box 62, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 19 to 293.
    - Lists, 1916–1917; HaleGE_02_0C_062_11; 54 pages (Box 62, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 294 to 348.
    - Committee on Policies, 1930–1934; HaleGE_02_0C_062_12; 306 pages (Box 62, Folder 12)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 349 to 655.
    - National Research Fund, 1925–1928; undated; HaleGE_02_0C_063_01; 375 pages (Box 63, Folder 1–2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 656 to 1031.
    - Organization, 1918–1933; HaleGE_02_0C_063_03; 306 pages (Box 63, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 1032 to 1339.
    - Reports, 1908–1918; HaleGE_02_0C_063_04; 249 pages (Box 63, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 1340 to 1589.
    - Rules and Constitution, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_063_05; 19 pages (Box 63, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 1590 to 1609.
    - Science Advisory Board, 1935; HaleGE_02_0C_063_06; 7 pages (Box 63, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 1610 to 1617.
    - Science and Research Department of the Bureau of Aircraft Production, undated; HaleGE_02_0C_063_07; 15 pages (Box 63, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 54, frames 1618 to 1634.
  - Other Organizations, 1895–1937; 4; 1 linear feet (Carton 2, Reel 55–67, Carton 4)
    - A: Industrial firms, 1904–1932; HaleGE_02_0D_064_01; 59 pages (Box 64, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 20 to 79.
    - Abstracts, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_064_02; 166 pages (Box 64, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 80 to 246.
    - Academy for Humanities, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_064_03; 20 pages (Box 64, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 247 to 267.
    - Adler Planetarium and Astronomical Museum, 1928–1930; HaleGE_02_0D_064_04; 69 pages (Box 64, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 268 to 337.
    - Amateur Telescope Makers Society, 1928; HaleGE_02_0D_064_05; 3 pages (Box 64, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 338 to 341.
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1901–1922; HaleGE_02_0D_064_06; 19 pages (Box 64, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 342 to 361.
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1901–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_064_07; 49 pages (Box 64, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 362 to 411.
    - American Academy of Engineers, 1915–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_064_08; 79 pages (Box 64, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 412 to 491.
    - Commission of Order of Leopold II, Academie Royale de Belgique, 1920–1922; HaleGE_02_0D_064_09; 10 pages (Box 64, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 492 to 503.
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1902–1903; HaleGE_02_0D_064_10; 657 pages (Box 64, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 55, frames 504 to 1161.
    - American Association of Variable Star Observers, 1922; HaleGE_02_0D_065_01; 9 pages (Box 65, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 19 to 28.
    - American Astronomical Society, 1902–1933; HaleGE_02_0D_065_02; 223 pages (Box 65, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 29 to 252.
    - American Institute of Consulting Engineers, 1916; HaleGE_02_0D_065_03; 4 pages (Box 65, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 253 to 257.
    - American Geophysical Union, 1919–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_065_04; 292 pages (Box 65, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 258 to 549.
    - American Geophysical Union Section of Terrestrial Magnetism and Electricity, 1921–1922; HaleGE_02_0D_065_05; 19 pages (Box 65, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 550 to 568.
    - American Geophysical Union Latitude Station at Ukiah, California, 1921–1922; HaleGE_02_0D_065_06; 134 pages (Box 65, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 569 to 703.
    - American Journal of Physical Anthropology, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_065_07; 5 pages (Box 65, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 704 to 709.
    - American Metric Association, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_065_08; 57 pages (Box 65, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 710 to 767.
    - American Museum of Natural History, 1919–1937; HaleGE_02_0D_065_09; 121 pages (Box 65, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 768 to 889.
    - American Philosophical Society, 1905–1937; HaleGE_02_0D_065_10; 298 pages (Box 65, Folder 10, Box 66, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 56, frames 890 to 1189.
    - American Oriental Society, 1920–1922; HaleGE_02_0D_066_02; 27 pages (Box 66, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 20 to 47.
    - American Physical Society, 1914–1933; HaleGE_02_0D_066_03; 57 pages (Box 66, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 48 to 105.
    - American Relief Association, 1921–1922; HaleGE_02_0D_066_04; 11 pages (Box 66, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 106 to 117.
    - Annandale Golf Club, 1916–1926; HaleGE_02_0D_066_05; 115 pages (Box 66, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 118 to 233.
    - Associated Press, 1916; HaleGE_02_0D_066_06; 3 pages (Box 66, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 234 to 237.
    - Astronomical and Astrophysical Society of America, 1902; HaleGE_02_0D_066_07; 1 pages (Box 66, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 238 to 239.
    - Astronomical and Astrophysical Society of France, 1904–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_066_08; 112 pages (Box 66, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 240 to 352.
    - Astronomical Society of Italy, 1914; HaleGE_02_0D_066_09; 5 pages (Box 66, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 353 to 358.
    - Astronomical Society of Mexico, 1908–1909; HaleGE_02_0D_066_10; 13 pages (Box 66, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 359 to 372.
    - Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 1901–1934; HaleGE_02_0D_066_11; 124 pages (Box 66, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 373 to 497.
    - Athenaeum, Pasadena, 1930–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_066_12; 44 pages (Box 66, Folder 12)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 498 to 542.
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1927–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_066_13; 11 pages (Box 66, Folder 13)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 543 to 554.
    - Automobile Club of Southern California, 1914–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_066_14; 62 pages (Box 66, Folder 14)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 555 to 617.
    - Beloit College, 1902–1912; HaleGE_02_0D_066_15; 159 pages (Box 66, Folder 15)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 618 to 776.
    - Bell Telephone Company, 1925–1927; HaleGE_02_0D_067_01; 10 pages (Box 67, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 777 to 787.
    - British Association for the Advancement of Science, 1903–1933; HaleGE_02_0D_067_02; 113 pages (Box 67, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 788 to 901.
    - British Astronomical Association, 1903–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_067_03; 27 pages (Box 67, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 902 to 929.
    - British Embassy, 1917–1918; HaleGE_02_0D_067_04; 6 pages (Box 67, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 930 to 936.
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1905–1919; HaleGE_02_0D_067_05; 40 pages (Box 67, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 937 to 977.
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1902–1915; HaleGE_02_0D_067_06; 9 pages (Box 67, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 978 to 987.
    - California Academy of Sciences, 1928; HaleGE_02_0D_067_07; 2 pages (Box 67, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 988 to 990.
    - California Institute of Technology, 1918–1928; HaleGE_02_0D_067_08; 280 pages (Box 67, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 57, frames 991 to 1272.
    - Carnegie Corp, 1918–1927; HaleGE_02_0D_067_09; .04 linear feet (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Caxton Club, 1912–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_067_10; 9 pages (Box 67, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 20 to 29.
    - Chamber of Commerce and Civic Association, 1919–1933; HaleGE_02_0D_067_11; 123 pages (Box 67, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 30 to 154.
    - Chicago Astronomical Society, 1932; HaleGE_02_0D_067_12; 6 pages (Box 67, Folder 12)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 155 to 161.
    - Chicago Centenniel, 1928–1934; HaleGE_02_0D_067_13; 266 pages (Box 67, Folder 13)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 162 to 428.
    - Cities Service Company, 1916–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_068_01; 77 pages (Box 68, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 429 to 506.
    - Columbia University, 1908–1931; HaleGE_02_0D_068_02; 47 pages (Box 68, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 507 to 554.
    - Commonwealth Club of California, 1916–1917; HaleGE_02_0D_068_03; 43 pages (Box 68, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 555 to 598.
    - Department of Commerce, 1916; HaleGE_02_0D_068_04; 1 pages (Box 68, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 599 to 600.
    - Concilium Bibliographicum, 1921; HaleGE_02_0D_068_05; 6 pages (Box 68, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 601 to 607.
    - Congress of Arts and Sciences, 1904–1905; HaleGE_02_0D_068_06; 4 pages (Box 68, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 608 to 612.
    - Consolidation of Government Science under Smithsonian Institution, 1921; HaleGE_02_0D_068_07; 1 pages (Box 68, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 613 to 614.
    - Constrast in Stellar Evolution, 1902–1903; HaleGE_02_0D_068_08; 7 pages (Box 68, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 615 to 622.
    - Copley Medal, Royal Society, 1932–1933; HaleGE_02_0D_068_09; 99 pages (Box 68, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 623 to 722.
    - Dalton Manufacturing Company, 1918; HaleGE_02_0D_068_10; 4 pages (Box 68, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 723 to 727.
    - Daniel Giraud Elliott Gold Medal, 1916; HaleGE_02_0D_068_11; 5 pages (Box 68, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 728 to 733.
    - Drake, Riley and Thomas, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0D_068_12; 19 pages (Box 68, Folder 12)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 58, frames 734 to 753.
    - Egypt Exploration Fund Society, 1912–1928; HaleGE_02_0D_068_13; 66 pages (Box 68, Folder 13)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 20 to 86.
    - Elliot and Fry, 1905–1912; HaleGE_02_0D_068_14; 5 pages (Box 68, Folder 14)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 87 to 92.
    - Encyclopedia Brittannica, 1905–1936; HaleGE_02_0D_068_15; 90 pages (Box 68, Folder 15)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 93 to 183.
    - Engineering News Record, 1918; HaleGE_02_0D_068_16; 6 pages (Box 68, Folder 16)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 184 to 190.
    - English Speaking Union, 1919–1927; HaleGE_02_0D_068_17; 59 pages (Box 68, Folder 17)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 191 to 250.
    - Exhibits, 1920; HaleGE_02_0D_068_18; 3 pages (Box 68, Folder 18)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 251 to 254.
    - First National Bank, Pasadena, 1914–1934; HaleGE_02_0D_068_19; 22 pages (Box 68, Folder 19)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 255 to 277.
    - Fodd Research Institute, 1921; HaleGE_02_0D_068_20; 6 pages (Box 68, Folder 20)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 278 to 284.
    - Foreign Shipments, 1911–1913; HaleGE_02_0D_068_21; 14 pages (Box 68, Folder 21)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 285 to 299.
    - Franklin Institute, 1916–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_068_22; 108 pages (Box 68, Folder 22)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 300 to 408.
    - Griffith Planetarium, 1930–1936; HaleGE_02_0D_068_23; 25 pages (Box 68, Folder 23)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 409 to 435.
    - Half Moon, 1908–1926; HaleGE_02_0D_069_01; 65 pages (Box 69, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 436 to 501.
    - Hall of Fame, 1920–1924; HaleGE_02_0D_069_02; 176 pages (Box 69, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 502 to 679.
    - Hall of Fame election of 1920, HaleGE_02_0D_069_03; 460 pages (Box 69, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 59, frames 680 to 1133.
    - Harper Brothers, 1907–1930; HaleGE_02_0D_069_04; 53 pages (Box 69, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 20 to 73.
    - Hamburg-American Line, 1907; HaleGE_02_0D_069_05; 7 pages (Box 69, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 74 to 81.
    - Harris Trust and Savings Bank, 1903–1909; HaleGE_02_0D_069_06; 34 pages (Box 69, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 82 to 116.
    - Harvard Club, 1914–1934; HaleGE_02_0D_069_07; 58 pages (Box 69, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 117 to 175.
    - Harvard University, 1919–1936; HaleGE_02_0D_069_08; 12 pages (Box 69, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 176 to 188.
    - Herschel Centenary, 1922; HaleGE_02_0D_069_09; 6 pages (Box 69, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 189 to 195.
    - Huntington Memorial Hospital, 1927; HaleGE_02_0D_069_10; 3 pages (Box 69, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 196 to 199.
    - History of Science Society (Isis), 1923–1924; HaleGE_02_0D_069_11; 42 pages (Box 69, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 200 to 242.
    - Illinois Trust and Savings Bank, 1904–1919; HaleGE_02_0D_070_01; 122 pages (Box 70, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 243 to 365.
    - Indian Association for the Cultivation of Science, 1929–1933; HaleGE_02_0D_070_02; 7 pages (Box 70, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 366 to 373.
    - Institute for Advanced Study, 1932–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_070_03; 11 pages (Box 70, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 374 to 385.
    - Institut de France, 1914–1931; HaleGE_02_0D_070_04; 20 pages (Box 70, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 386 to 406.
    - Institute of International Education, 1931–1936; HaleGE_02_0D_070_05; 7 pages (Box 70, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 407 to 414.
    - Institute of Public Relations, 1927–1928; HaleGE_02_0D_070_06; 25 pages (Box 70, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 415 to 440.
    - Insurance, 1904–1910; HaleGE_02_0D_070_07; 37 pages (Box 70, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 441 to 478.
    - Investigators Club, 1902–1903; HaleGE_02_0D_070_08; 26 pages (Box 70, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 479 to 506.
    - Investment Circulars, 1928–1935; HaleGE_02_0D_070_09; 75 pages (Box 70, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 507 to 582.
    - Italian Society of Sciences, 1919; HaleGE_02_0D_070_10; 2 pages (Box 70, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 60, frames 583 to 585.